Educators and business leaders have more in common than it may seem.
教育工作者和企业领导者的共同点，比人们可能以为的要多。
Teachers want to prepare students for a successful future.
教师希望让学生为成功的未来做好准备。
Technology companies have an interest in developing a workforce with the STEM (science, technology, engineering and math) skills needed to grow the company and advance the industry.
科技公司有意培养一支劳动力队伍，使其具备发展壮大公司、推动行业进步所需的STEM（科学、技术、工程和数学）技能。
How can they work together to achieve these goals?
双方如何才能携手实现这些目标呢？
Play may be the answer.
玩耍或许就是答案。
Focusing on STEM skills is important, but the reality is that STEM skills are enhanced and more relevant when combined with traditional, hands-on creative activities.
注重STEM技能固然重要，但现实情况是，STEM技能与传统的、亲自动手的创造性活动结合起来时，会得到增强，也更有实际意义。
This combination is proving to be the best way to prepare today’s children to be the makers and builders of tomorrow.
事实日益证明，要让如今的孩子做好准备，成为未来的创客和建造者，这种结合是最好的办法。
That is why technology companies are partnering with educators to bring back good old-fashioned play.
正因如此，科技公司正与教育工作者合作，让传统的玩耍方式重新回归。
In fact many experts argue that the most important 21st-century skills aren’t related to specific technologies or subject matter, but to creativity: skills like imagination, problem-finding and problem-solving, teamwork, optimism, patience and the ability to experiment and take risks.
事实上，许多专家认为，21世纪最重要的技能与具体的技术或学科内容无关，而与创造力有关，这类技能包括想象力、发现问题和解决问题的能力、团队合作、乐观、耐心，以及尝试和冒险的能力。
These are skills acquired when kids tinker.
这些是孩子们在鼓捣小玩意时习得的技能。
High-tech organizations such as NASA’s Jet Propulsion Laboratory have found that their best overall problem solvers were master tinkerers in their youth.
美国国家航空航天局喷气推进实验室等高科技机构发现，机构中解决问题综合能力最强的人，年轻时曾是鼓捣小玩意的高手。
There are cognitive benefits of doing things the way we did as children—building something, tearing it down, then building it up again.
像我们小时候那样做事，对认知有好处：搭建一样东西，把它拆掉，然后再重新搭起来。
Research shows that given 15 minutes of free play, four- and five-year-olds will spend a third of this time engaged in spatial, mathematical, and architectural activities.
研究表明，如果给四五岁的孩子15分钟的自由玩耍时间，他们会用其中三分之一的时间从事空间、数学和建筑类活动。
This type of play—especially with building blocks—helps children discover and develop key principles in math and geometry.
这类玩耍，尤其是搭积木，有助于孩子发现并逐步掌握数学和几何中的关键原理。
If play and building are critical to 21st-century skill development, that’s really good news for two reasons: Children are born builders, makers, and creators, so fostering 21st-century skills may be as simple as giving kids room to play, tinker and try things out, even as they grow older.
如果玩耍和搭建对21世纪技能的发展至关重要，那么这真是个好消息，原因有二：孩子天生就是建造者、创客和创造者，因此，培养21世纪技能或许简单到只需给孩子留出空间，让他们去玩耍、鼓捣、尝试各种东西就行，哪怕他们渐渐长大也依然如此。
Secondly, it doesn’t take 21st-century technology to foster 21st-century skills.
其次，培养21世纪技能并不需要21世纪的技术。
This is especially important for under-resourced schools and communities.
这对资源不足的学校和社区来说尤为重要。
Taking whatever materials are handy and tinkering with them is a simple way to engage those important “maker” skills.
手边有什么材料就拿来鼓捣一番，是调动那些重要“创客”技能的一种简单方法。
And anyone, anywhere, can do it.
而且无论是谁、无论在哪里，都能做到。